<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>In Memoriam of Guntars Gedulis on Guntars Gedulis</title>
    <link>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in In Memoriam of Guntars Gedulis on Guntars Gedulis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 16:31:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Package from Venezuela</title>
      <link>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/the-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/the-package/</guid>
      <description>Original in Vitauts Take 19: The Package from Venezuela. Published in 30/11/2015.
A week or so ago, I came home from lunch and dad was a bit excited about the mail. I asked him what it was, and he showed me a package from Venezuela. “Who do you know in Venezuela,” I asked.
He looked at the name and thought aloud, “Guntars Gedulis… Guntars Gedulis…” He paused and said, “I knew him from the camps in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaudeamus Sociedad Venezolana De Canto</title>
      <link>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/gaudeamus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/gaudeamus/</guid>
      <description>Published on October 15, 2011
25 years, 1987 – 2012
by Guntars Gedulis, conductor and composer
The Gaudeamus Venezuelan Singing Society was founded in Caracas in January 1987 and, while centering its activities there, organizes events throughout the country. Gaudeamus is dedicated to the training of Venezuelan singers through artistic and educational programs. Its members include vocal groups and solo artists, choral singers, conductors, music teachers and persons in related fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthology of Latvian Choral Music XII: Journeys of the Soul (1940-2000)</title>
      <link>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/anthology-latvian-choral-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/anthology-latvian-choral-music/</guid>
      <description>Composers:
 Ilze Arne (1953) Viktors Bastiks (1912 - 2001) Pauls Dambis (1936) Rihards Dubra (1964) Maija Einfelde (1939) Guntars Gedulis (1952) Romualds Jermaks (1931) Alberts Jērums (1919 - 1978) Janis Kalnins (1904 - 2000) Talivaldis Kenins (1919 - 2008) Arturs Maskats (1957) Imants Mezaraups (1958 - 2013) Jānis Norvilis (1906 - 1994) Peteris Plakidis (1947 - 2017) Arvīds Purvs (1926) Imants Ramiņš (1943) Eduards Šēnfelds (1907 - 1990) Bruno Skulte (1905 - 1976) Pēteris Vasks (1946) Andris Vītoliņš (1931)  Editor: Arnolds Klotiņš (1934)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guntars&#39; Biography (Part II)</title>
      <link>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/biography-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/biography-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Music is a window to a different, spiritual world; a bridge that brings us out of the everyday and joins us with the experience.&amp;rdquo; (Guntars Gudelis)
The composer, conductor, singer, teacher and active Latvian community member Guntars Gedulis was born on August 27th, 1952 in New York, the United States. His first musical impressions were received from his father, singer Visvaldis Gedulis. From an early age he learned to play the piano, later clarinet, performing in school orchestras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guntar&#39;s Biography (Part I)</title>
      <link>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/biography-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andreispurim.github.io/Gedulis/blog/biography-1/</guid>
      <description>Guntars Gedulis was born of Latvian parents in Manhattan, where he received his basic education. He has resided in Venezuela since 1975, and works as a composer, conductor, music educator, singer and organizer of musical events.
Beginning piano and clarinet studies at an early age, he graduated from The High School of Music and Art (music composition) and The City College of New York (CUNY), where he studied conducting and with the composers Miriam Gideon and Mario Davidovsky.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>